Imagine a future where we can tuck into meat, but no animals have been sacrificed in the process.
想象一下，未来我们可以大快朵颐地吃肉，但在这个过程中没有动物被杀害。
16% of the UK population enjoy a meat-free diet, according to statistics website Finder.com.
根据统计网站Finder.com的数据，英国16%的人口喜欢无肉饮食。
It seems there is an appeal in lab-grown meat as an alternative to traditional meat consumption.
实验室培育的肉作为传统肉类消费的替代品似乎很有吸引力。
But, despite years of anticipation, this futuristic food is still not on our plates.
但是，尽管经过了多年的期待，这种未来主义的食物仍然没有出现在我们的餐盘上。
Why?
为什么？
One of the biggest reasons is cost.
最主要的原因之一是成本。
The first ever lab-grown hamburger was unveiled in 2013 by Dutch scientist Mark Post.
2013年，荷兰科学家马克·波斯特首次揭开了世界上第一个实验室培育汉堡的神秘面纱。
It was created from beef cells and cost more than $300,000.
它是用牛肉细胞制成的，成本超过30万美元。
Lab-grown meat production stretches from thousands to hundreds of thousands of US dollars per ounce – that's the weight of about two chicken nuggets.
实验室培育肉的生产成本从每盎司数千美元到数十万美元不等——这大约是两块鸡块的重量。
This expense is partly due to the cost of raw materials that 'feed' the cells – a combination of sugar, proteins and other nutrients are added to the cells.
这笔费用部分源于"喂养"细胞的原材料成本——糖、蛋白质和其他营养物质的组合被添加到细胞中。
In 2023, US-based company Upside Foods received approval from the US Department of Agriculture and the Food and Drug Administration to start selling lab-grown meat.
2023年，总部位于美国的Upside Foods公司获得了美国农业部以及食品药品监督管理局的批准，开始销售实验室培育肉。
In order to do this, the company has had to take on significant economic losses so that they can price it fairly compared to traditional meat.
为了做到这一点，该公司不得不承受重大的经济损失，以便能与传统肉类相比定价持平。
An investor in Upside Food, Lisa Feria, told Forbes magazine "Profitability is very much years off because the biggest challenge ahead of them is can we make it at millions of tons a year and ultimately remotely compete with conventional meat".
Upside Foods的投资者丽莎·费里亚告诉《福布斯》杂志："盈利还需要很多年，因为他们面临的最大挑战是我们能否每年生产数百万吨，并最终与传统肉类展开竞争。"
There are also environmental costs.
还有环境成本。
A 2023 study by the University of California found that the process of producing lab-grown meat could have a four to 25 times higher impact on global warming than beef, which is generally the highest-polluting meat.
加州大学2023年的一项研究发现，生产实验室培育肉的过程对全球变暖的影响可能是牛肉的四到25倍，而牛肉通常是对环境破坏最严重的肉类。
This is mostly because of the emissions needed to create 'feed'.
这主要是由于制造"饲料"所需的排放。
So, it seems unlikely that we'll be eating lab-grown meat just yet, and we possibly never will.
所以，我们似乎还不太可能吃到实验室培育的肉，而且我们可能永远也不会吃（心理层面）。